# LOUISE FATTON

#### DEVELOPER



#### CONTACT

0041.78.778.70.38



louise.fatton@hotmail.fr



https://lfatton.github.io/



Fahys 7, 2000 Neuchâtel, Switzerland

#### EDUCATION

#### 42 CURSUS

Computer Science 42 Paris 2018 - 2022

#### **ERASMUS**

English Language and Literature University of Leeds 2014 — 2015

#### **BACHELOR OF ARTS**

English Language and Literature & Japanese studies University of Geneva 2012 - 2016

# SKILLS

#### | Technical

C / C# / C++

MVC ASP.Net / SQL Server

HTML5 / Less / JavaScript / jQuery

Unity / OpenGL / PixiJS / Vue3

Git / Makefile / Unix

#### SUMMARY

Fast learning and passionate software developer with 3 years of experience working in a tech company, I also have taken part in several graphical and game projects. I mainly worked with small teams on those projects, thus gaining experience in various areas of development ranging from programming a ray casting engine to working on gameplays and HUDs. I have recently joined a Unity 2D platformer project on which I am working during my free time.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

UDITIS S.A. | 2019 — 2022

Uditis is a 23-year-old company specialising in digital technology based in Peseux, Neuchâtel. It offers web-based solutions and applications as well as IT support. Uditis joined Sequotech Group at the start of 2022 and currently has 65 employees.

- · Started as an intern for 6 months, mainly helping improve their inhouse CMS and working solo on a projects management solution from scratch, before being offered a permanent position as a developer.
- · Worked on several different projects of varying team size, ranging from 1 to 10 people.
- Last worked on 2 different projects in C# MVC ASP.Net, while also being part of a team that was dedicated to the CSEM (Swiss Center for Electronics and Microtechnology); maintaining their intranet and developing new applications (in JavaScript) curtailed to their needs.

### FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER

Absinthe&Basilic Restaurant | 2019

Absinthe&Basilic was a restaurant based in Fleurier, Neuchâtel. It unfortunately closed after the first COVID-19 lockdown.

• Migrated their website on WordPress and incorporated the new design.

# PASSENGER SERVICE AGENT

Swissport International AG | 2015 — 2016

Swissport is one of the leading companies providing ground services to

- Student job during my last year at the University of Geneva.
- Part of the section dedicated only to the low-cost airline EasyJet and worked first at the check-in during charter season, before moving on to working at the gates as well.
- Mostly worked on the early shifts (from 4AM to 12.30PM) as I did not mind the change in rhythm and the morning team was really nice.

# LOUISE

#### DEVELOPER

#### SKILLS

#### | Spoken languages

French - Native language

English - Fluent

Japanese, German - Basic knowledge

#### HOBBIES

#### My first games

Pokémon Gold Worms 3D

#### **Currently playing**

Zelda: The Tears of the Kingdom Cyberpunk 2077

# Spent a lot of time on

Skyrim
The Witcher 3
Zelda: Breath of the Wild
The Sims 4

#### Fun with friends

Battleblock Theater Animal Crossing: New Horizons Overcooked 2

#### Obsessed with

Stardew Valley ♥ Hades Horizon Zero Dawn Assassin's Creed Black Flag

#### When not playing

Pole dancing Reading and cooking

#### MOST RELEVANT PROJECTS

#### AKU - REBIRTH OF SHADOWS

OuatStudios | Current

A 2D platformer unity game project, in development since 2019 and nominated in the 2022 Pro Helvetia's She Got Game selection.

• Joined the project last May as the new lead developer and worked since on game mechanics ameliorations and a small demo.

#### DOOM-NUKEM

42 Project | 2019

The goal was to create a game engine in C based on a mix of Doom and Quake (Duke Nukem) engines using ray casting. We had to make a map editor and a map to binary file compressor as well.

 Including my working career, this is the biggest and more complex project I have worked on, it took us approximately 6 months with a team of 4 people to make.

#### SCOP

42 Project | 2023

A 3D modeling project in OpenGL4.6 and C++17. It is a small program that parses a wavefront .obj and renders it on screen.

• Developed mostly alone and it helped me get a good grasp on shaders, OpenGL, and the math (especially matrices) behind 3D modeling.

#### TERMINAL VELOCITY: SHARKINATOR 2000

UPsi Jam | 2023

A 3D FPS platformer kind of game made with Unreal5, where you must reach the top of the level by shooting on the ground and walls.

- Made in 42 hours with a team of 4 on the given theme 'it's not supposed to do that'.
- Responsible of creating enemies with basic Al, managing player health, as well as implementing the game menu and victory screen.

# SYSYPHUS

Epic Game Jam | 2019

First game jam. Rhythmic rogue like game where you play a bird moving a moon up a mountain, developed in JavaScript and PixiJS.

• Made in 2 days with a team of 5 on the given theme 'death'.

# EXTRA

#### ONE OF THE FOUNDING MEMBERS OF AU BÛCHER

An intersectional feminist collective created at the end of 2021. Since then, the collective has been part of various feminist events during the last two years and even organised a one-day festival for women and queer people in May 2022.